<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DARSA</title>
    <link>https://darsa.info/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://darsa.info/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>DARSA</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2030 13:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://darsa.info/media/icon_hua8526f2966cb9e7d5f57c97e290bdf30_76380_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>DARSA</title>
      <link>https://darsa.info/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>QGG</title>
      <link>https://darsa.info/collaborators/qgg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://darsa.info/collaborators/qgg/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dev Mehrotra</title>
      <link>https://darsa.info/people/auto-devd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://darsa.info/people/auto-devd/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;people-dates&#34;&gt; From 2025-06-02 to 2028-05-31&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dev Mehrotra&lt;/strong&gt; is currently pursuing a PhD at Aarhus University in machine learning, sensor development, and computational biology. He holds a Master’s in Computer Science from the University of Wisconsin–Madison. His research focuses on &lt;a href=&#34;https://darsa.info/project/global-worming/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;global worming&lt;/a&gt;., specifically developing methods to track earthworms underground to better understand soil health. Dev’s work bridges computer science, agriculture, and environmental science to create data-driven solutions for real-world challenges.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markus Dahl Lauritsen</title>
      <link>https://darsa.info/people/auto-mdlauritsen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://darsa.info/people/auto-mdlauritsen/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;people-dates&#34;&gt; From 2025-01-15 to 2028-01-14&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Markus Lauritsen is a Ph.D. student in the DARSA group at Aarhus University, focusing on plant phenomics and AI-driven environmental response mapping. He earned his Bachelor of Science in Engineering (Robot Systems) in 2020 and his Master of Science in Engineering (Robot Systems) with a profile in Advanced Robotics Technology in 2022, both at the University of Southern Denmark.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Passionate about integrating AI—particularly computer vision—and his knowledge of mechanical design and electronics, Markus’s Ph.D. research centers on developing high-throughput phenotyping tools, including the Duckweed Automatic Robot for Phenomics (DWARPH), to study plant responses across complex environmental conditions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A dedicated maker with a profound interest in nature and the outdoors, Markus combines technical innovation with ecological curiosity to bridge technology and biology, contributing to the future of sustainable agriculture.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HFSP postdoctoral fellowship program</title>
      <link>https://darsa.info/opportunities/hfsp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://darsa.info/opportunities/hfsp/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marie Skłodowska-Curie Actions postdoctoral fellowship</title>
      <link>https://darsa.info/opportunities/msca/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://darsa.info/opportunities/msca/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marta Vittrup</title>
      <link>https://darsa.info/people/auto-mgomez/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://darsa.info/people/auto-mgomez/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;people-dates&#34;&gt; From 2023-12-01 to 2027-09-30&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marta is a master / Ph.D. student with background in Data Science. Her project is to help to classify earthworms with the help of deep learning in order to restore the soil.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Melika Baghooee</title>
      <link>https://darsa.info/people/auto-mbaghooee/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://darsa.info/people/auto-mbaghooee/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;people-dates&#34;&gt; From 2023-06-01 to 2026-06-30&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Melika is a Ph.D. student at QGG (Aarhus University). She holds a background in Biosystems Engineering and is interested in developing tools to enhance agricultural systems and drive a digital green transition that could make agriculture more sustainable, resilient, and productive. Her Ph.D. project aims to develop novel algorithms and annotation tools for hierarchical classification, which have profound and immediate applications to agriculture and ecology.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zixuan He</title>
      <link>https://darsa.info/people/auto-zhe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://darsa.info/people/auto-zhe/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;people-dates&#34;&gt; From 2025-01-06 to 2027-01-05&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zixuan is a Postdoc researcher in &lt;a href=&#34;https://qgg.au.dk&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;the QGG&lt;/a&gt; group, at &lt;a href=&#34;https://international.au.dk/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Aarhus University&lt;/a&gt;.
His present research, &lt;a href=&#34;https://darsa.info/project/global-worming/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;global worming&lt;/a&gt;, is for unveiling the hidden but critical role of earthworms in agroecological systems through the innovative application of deep learning and remote sensing technologies..
He finished his bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in automation from &lt;a href=&#34;https://english.scau.edu.cn/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;South Chian Agricultural University&lt;/a&gt; in June 2019 and Ph.D. degree in Biological and Agricultural Engineering from &lt;a href=&#34;https://agrobotics.cals.cornell.edu/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Agricultural Automation and Robotics Lab&lt;/a&gt; at &lt;a href=&#34;https://bsyse.wsu.edu/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Washington State University&lt;/a&gt; in May 2024. During his Ph.D., he was mainly responsible for one robotics strawberry harvesting project including hardware design and adaptive AI machine vision and participated in various projects such as soft manipulator and precision irrigation.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helena Russello</title>
      <link>https://darsa.info/people/auto-hrussello/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://darsa.info/people/auto-hrussello/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;people-dates&#34;&gt; From 2024-08-01 to 2026-07-31&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Helena is a Postdoc researcher in &lt;a href=&#34;https://qgg.au.dk&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;the QGG&lt;/a&gt; group, at &lt;a href=&#34;https://international.au.dk/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Aarhus University&lt;/a&gt;.
Her background is in computer science and applied (deep) machine learning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During her PhD in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.wur.nl/en/research-results/chair-groups/plant-sciences/agricultural-biosystems-engineering.htm&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Agricultural Biosystems Engineering&lt;/a&gt; group at the Wageningen University &amp;amp; Research, Helena developed computer-vision methods for automatic lameness detection in dairy cows.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Helena’s research interests lie in applications of computer vision and machine learning for conservation and wildlife monitoring.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Høye Lab</title>
      <link>https://darsa.info/collaborators/hoye-lab/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://darsa.info/collaborators/hoye-lab/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quentin Geissmann</title>
      <link>https://darsa.info/people/auto-qgeissmann/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://darsa.info/people/auto-qgeissmann/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;people-dates&#34;&gt; From 2022-09-01 to present&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quentin, assistant professor in &lt;a href=&#34;https://qgg.au.dk&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;the QGG&lt;/a&gt;, in &lt;a href=&#34;https://international.au.dk/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Aarhus University&lt;/a&gt; is the Principal Investigator of the DARSA group. His background is both in insect physiology and computational biology.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During his PhD at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.imperial.ac.uk/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Imperial College London&lt;/a&gt;, in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://lab.gilest.ro/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Gilestro Lab&lt;/a&gt;, he built an open-source automatic insect behaviour monitoring platform.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In his Postdoc, at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ubc.ca/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;UBC&lt;/a&gt;, with the &lt;a href=&#34;https://haneylab.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Haney Lab&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href=&#34;https://piee-lab.landfood.ubc.ca/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;PIEE Lab&lt;/a&gt;, he developed AI-powered smart traps to monitor insects and study their relationships with plants and microbes in agroecological contexts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quentin&amp;rsquo;s interests in machine learning and sustainable agriculture led him to start the DARSA Group in Aarhus in September 2022.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Example Talk</title>
      <link>https://darsa.info/talk/example-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2030 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://darsa.info/talk/example-talk/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Click on the &lt;strong&gt;Slides&lt;/strong&gt; button above to view the built-in slides feature.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slides can be added in a few ways:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Create&lt;/strong&gt; slides using Wowchemy&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/docs/managing-content/#create-slides&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Slides&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; feature and link using &lt;code&gt;slides&lt;/code&gt; parameter in the front matter of the talk file&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Upload&lt;/strong&gt; an existing slide deck to &lt;code&gt;static/&lt;/code&gt; and link using &lt;code&gt;url_slides&lt;/code&gt; parameter in the front matter of the talk file&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Embed&lt;/strong&gt; your slides (e.g. Google Slides) or presentation video on this page using &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/docs/writing-markdown-latex/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;shortcodes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Further event details, including &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/docs/writing-markdown-latex/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;page elements&lt;/a&gt; such as image galleries, can be added to the body of this page.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Huangjing Qin</title>
      <link>https://darsa.info/people/auto-huangjing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://darsa.info/people/auto-huangjing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;people-dates&#34;&gt; From 2025-09-01 to 2026-01-31&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Huangjing is a Master’s student in Computer Engineering at Aarhus University. She is doing her thesis with DARSA, working on deep learning and computer vision applied to plants, animals, and agriculture and always open to learning more about nature.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FlatBug</title>
      <link>https://darsa.info/project/flatbug/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://darsa.info/project/flatbug/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robert Thalheim</title>
      <link>https://darsa.info/people/auto-rthalheim/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://darsa.info/people/auto-rthalheim/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;people-dates&#34;&gt; From 2025-01-20 to 2025-07-15&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NA&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DWARPH</title>
      <link>https://darsa.info/project/dwarph/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://darsa.info/project/dwarph/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;DWARPH is a 3-year &lt;a href=&#34;https://dff.dk/en/front-page?set_language=en&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;DFF Sapere-Aude&lt;/a&gt; project on aiming at automating duckweed growth and observation to perform experiment on plant biology at high-throughput.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Plants live in multivariate environments (light, temperature, etc.), ultimately constraining their fitness. Although “phenomics” upscales the measurement of fitness (i.e., the “response”), most work only considers a few environmental values. “Metaphenomics”, instead, integrates whole response “surfaces” (RSs)—over a range of environments—, providing novel insight into plasticity, specialisation and resilience. However, conceptual and methodological limitations have so far hindered the study of RSs. Our three-part project presents a novel paradigm to tackle this issue. i) We use duckweed, a tiny, fast-growing plant and develop an automatic miniature growth chamber that scores growth and can update itself. ii) We create an AI-inspired methodology that plans experiments in real time. iii) We describe the RSs of a genetically diverse duckweed panel to discover the structure and basic biology of RSs. Altogether, our project sheds light on unexplored aspects of plant biology.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PhD in Plant Phenomics: AI and Robotics for High-Throughput Environmental Response Mapping</title>
      <link>https://darsa.info/post/2024-dwarph-phd/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://darsa.info/post/2024-dwarph-phd/</guid>
      <description>















&lt;figure  id=&#34;figure-duckweed-automatic-robot-for-phenotyping&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;d-flex justify-content-center&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;w-100&#34; &gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://darsa.info/DWARPH.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;DuckWeed Automatic Robot for PHenotyping&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; data-zoomable /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      DuckWeed Automatic Robot for PHenotyping
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;open-phd-position&#34;&gt;Open PhD Position&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please also see the &lt;a href=&#34;https://phd.tech.au.dk/for-applicants/apply-here/saeropslag/phd-in-plant-phenomics-ai-and-robotics-for-high-throughput-environmental-response-mapping&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;official posting&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;strong&gt;Deadline: 15 Nov 2024&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;project-summary&#34;&gt;Project Summary&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are seeking a highly motivated PhD student to work on an exciting multidisciplinary project funded by the Danish Council for Independent Research (Sapere Aude), aiming to develop cutting-edge tools to understand complex plant responses to environmental variables.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;project-description&#34;&gt;Project Description&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;context&#34;&gt;Context&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Plants live in complex environments, responding to factors such as light, temperature, and nutrients, which affect their growth and survival. Each plant responds differently to these factors, and understanding these reactions is key to studying their ability to adapt and thrive in various conditions. This project aims to take a groundbreaking approach by not just studying plants in isolated environments, but by exploring how they grow across a multidimentional range of environmental conditions in real-time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;about-the-project&#34;&gt;About The Project&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The project focuses on characterising &amp;ldquo;response surfaces&amp;rdquo; in the small, fast-growing plant species Lemna gibba (duckweed), using high-throughput phenotyping and advanced AI tools. The core of the research involves:
• Development and validation of &lt;strong&gt;DWARPH&lt;/strong&gt; (DuckWeed Automatic Robot for Phenomics), a scalable, miniature growth chamber with automated real-time phenotyping.
• Application of &lt;strong&gt;deep learning&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;optimisation theory&lt;/strong&gt; to iteratively explore how environmental factors influence plant growth.
• Comparative analysis of genetic determinants of plant plasticity and ecological niche modelling across multiple L. gibba ecotypes.
This research will explore exciting questions about plant adaptation, response surface modeling, and experimental metaphenomics, providing valuable insights into plant biology and the future of sustainable agriculture.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;research-group&#34;&gt;Research Group&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will join the dynamic &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://darsa.info/&#34;&gt;Digital Approaches for Resilient and Sustainable Agriculture (DARSA) group&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, at the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://qgg.au.dk/en&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Center for Quantitative Genetics and Genomics (QGG)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. The group and center foster a dynamic, inclusive and multidisciplinary environment. Your research will take place at &lt;a href=&#34;https://international.au.dk/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Aarhus University&lt;/a&gt;, a prestigious institution located in a vibrant student-friendly city. This project will be conducted with local (the &lt;a href=&#34;https://bio.au.dk/en/about-biology/sections/aquatic-biology&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Aquatic Biology Section&lt;/a&gt;) and international (&lt;a href=&#34;https://cals.ncsu.edu/molecular-and-structural-biochemistry/people/ryan-sartor/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Dr. Ryan Sartor&lt;/a&gt;) collaborators.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;selection-process&#34;&gt;Selection Process&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Candidates will be evaluated based on their CV, motivation statement, and reference letters. Shortlisted candidates will be invited for an interview (online or in person). The top candidate will be offered the position.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;why-apply&#34;&gt;Why Apply?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be at the forefront of integrating technology and ecology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead original fundamental research on unknown aspects of plant biology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work in a collaborative and supportive research environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gain experience with cutting-edge technologies applied to research&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;applicants-profile-and-eligibility&#34;&gt;Applicant&amp;rsquo;s Profile and Eligibility&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The applicant should:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have completed a &lt;strong&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s degree&lt;/strong&gt; (before January 2025) in engineering or experimental science (e.g., ecology, biology, experimental physics, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have experience in developing &lt;strong&gt;advanced custom hardware&lt;/strong&gt; (PCB, 3d printing, CNC, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have advanced &lt;strong&gt;mathematical and programming skills&lt;/strong&gt; (in particular, experience working with scientific languages (e.g. R and Python)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Be familiar with image processing, imaging techniques&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have a strong interest and &lt;strong&gt;motivation to study plant biology and ecology&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possess advanced &lt;strong&gt;collaborative&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;interpersonal skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Be fluent in English (written and spoken)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;supervision&#34;&gt;Supervision&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our primary goal is for our students to succeed by helping them to develop and achieve their career goals. As such, we support and help students in taking the project in their own direction, within the original scope, and encourage flexibility as well as new viewpoints as the project moves forward. The successful applicant should expect a weekly meeting with &lt;a href=&#34;https://darsa.info/people/auto-qgeissmann&#34;&gt;Quentin Geissmann&lt;/a&gt;, their direct supervisor. Students are encouraged to collaborate within and outside of the group, and will be given (funded) opportunities to present their research at international conferences. We also consider it the supervisor’s role to ensure students feel safe and included in their work environment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;location-and-facilities&#34;&gt;Location and Facilities&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The research takes place in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://qgg.au.dk/en/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;QGG&lt;/a&gt; at &lt;a href=&#34;https://international.au.dk/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Aarhus University (AU)&lt;/a&gt;.
AU is a world-class university (the largest in Denmark), with outstanding opportunities for collaboration on this particular project.
For this project, we have access to various High-Performance Computing platforms and workstations, including GPUs.
In addition to these computational resources, we have  a workshop suitable to prototype hardware (cameras, edge computing, &amp;hellip;) in-house, and have access to larger infrastructure through our collaborations with the engineering department.
Aarhus itself is a vibrant city with an &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.theguardian.com/travel/2016/apr/05/aarhus-denmark-city-of-culture-2017&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;active cultural life&lt;/a&gt;, a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.visitaarhus.com/groups/study-aarhus&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;dynamic student community&lt;/a&gt; and a very high standard of living.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;administrative-considerations&#34;&gt;Administrative Considerations&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;timeline&#34;&gt;Timeline&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The application &lt;strong&gt;deadline is Nov 15th 2024&lt;/strong&gt;.
The expected start date is &lt;em&gt;January 1st, 2025&lt;/em&gt;, but this is somewhat flexible (as it may depend on personal situations, getting a visa, etc).
The total duration of the PhD is three years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;stipend&#34;&gt;Stipend&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The PhD salaries are set at the university level and defined in &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.hr.aau.dk/digitalAssets/1001/1001827_akademisk_skala_01.04.2021.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;this table&lt;/a&gt; &amp;ndash; the exact numbers depend on previous post-graduate work experience, and the taxation system is somewhat complicated, but expect to have a net salary of approximately 18,000 DKK (≈2,400 Euro) per month. Overall, Denmark is one of the countries where students &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.studyinternational.com/news/highest-phd-stipend/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;earn the most&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;application-process&#34;&gt;Application Process&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In order to ensure a fair assessment of all applicants, the graduate school implements an official procedure. Please refer to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://phd.tech.au.dk/for-applicants/apply-here/saeropslag/phd-in-plant-phenomics-ai-and-robotics-for-high-throughput-environmental-response-mapping&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;formal offer on the university&amp;rsquo;s website&lt;/a&gt;, which will direct you to an online form.
Candidates will be evaluated based on their CV, motivation statement, and reference letters. Shortlisted candidates will be invited for an interview (online or in person). The top candidate will be offered the position.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;questions&#34;&gt;Questions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, do not hesitate to &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:qgeissmann@qgg.au.dk&#34;&gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt; if you have questions, or want to discuss your interest, ideas&amp;hellip; When doing so, please &lt;em&gt;enclose a CV and a brief description of your motivation&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PhD in Agricultural Ecology and Machine Learning: An Underground Video Tracking System to Characterise Novel Earthworm-Plant Interactions</title>
      <link>https://darsa.info/post/2024-wormitron-phd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://darsa.info/post/2024-wormitron-phd/</guid>
      <description>















&lt;figure  id=&#34;figure-custom-imaging-platform-and-deep-learning-to-identify-and-phenotype-earthworms&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;d-flex justify-content-center&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;w-100&#34; &gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://darsa.info/wormitron.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Custom Imaging Platform and Deep Learning to Identify and Phenotype Earthworms&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; data-zoomable /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      Custom Imaging Platform and Deep Learning to Identify and Phenotype Earthworms
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;open-phd-position&#34;&gt;Open PhD Position&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please also see the &lt;a href=&#34;https://phd.tech.au.dk/for-applicants/apply-here/saeropslag/phd-in-agricultural-ecology-and-machine-learning-an-underground-video-tracking-system-to-characterise-novel-earthworm-plant-interactions&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;official posting&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;strong&gt;Deadline: 31 August 2024&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;project-summary&#34;&gt;Project Summary&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Start an innovative PhD focused on developing high-throughput methods using &lt;strong&gt;cameras and computer vision to explore the hidden world of earthworm-plant interactions&lt;/strong&gt;. Earthworms play a crucial ecological role, and this pioneering approach aims to uncover their interactions with plant roots. This project is the first phase of a comprehensive &lt;a href=&#34;https://researchleaderprogramme.com/recipients/quentin-geissmann/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;5-year initiative&lt;/a&gt; employing advanced technologies (imaging, acoustics, deep learning, remote sensing, etc.) to enhance our understanding of earthworms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;project-description&#34;&gt;Project Description&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;context&#34;&gt;Context&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Soil health is the foundation of our food systems, yet we are losing it at an alarming rate due to our land use. To combat this, we must shift from extractive to restorative, circular agriculture. This paradigm shift requires extensive research on decomposers, particularly earthworms. Earthworms are essential for soil health due to their ubiquity and biomass, but their subterranean lifestyle poses significant observational challenges. Recent advances in remote sensing and deep learning offer a unique opportunity to study these elusive organisms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;outcomes&#34;&gt;Outcomes&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a successful applicant, you will develop “The Wormitron,” an innovative, open-source hardware system featuring cameras and 2D-terrariums to image earthworms and plant roots continuously under semi-controlled conditions. You will test hypotheses on the nature, timing, and implications (both physiological and evolutionary) of earthworm-root interactions. This project promises direct applications for sustainable agriculture and a profound understanding of these hidden ecosystem engineers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;research-group&#34;&gt;Research Group&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The successful student will be integrated the growing &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://darsa.info/&#34;&gt;Digital Approaches for Resilient and Sustainable Agriculture (DARSA) group&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, started in 2022, at the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://qgg.au.dk/en&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Center for Quantitative Genetics and Genomics (QGG)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. Both the group and the centre are inclusive and multidisciplinary environments with a range of local and international collaborations. The research takes place at &lt;a href=&#34;https://international.au.dk&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Aarhus University&lt;/a&gt;, a world-leading institution located in a vibrant city.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;applicants-profile-and-eligibility&#34;&gt;Applicant&amp;rsquo;s Profile and Eligibility&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We believe that diversity makes us &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.pnas.org/doi/abs/10.1073/pnas.1700616114&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;better at tackling complex problems&lt;/a&gt;.
Therefore, we strongly support applicants with a diverse background and are committed to promote inclusion and equity.
Applicants must &lt;strong&gt;have completed a Master’s degree&lt;/strong&gt; (before January 2025) in experimental science (e.g., ecology, biology, engineering, experimental physics, etc.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have experience in &lt;strong&gt;planning and conducting laboratory experiments&lt;/strong&gt; (ideally, building custom setups).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have at least &lt;strong&gt;basic programming skills&lt;/strong&gt; (in particular, experience working with scientific languages (e.g. R and Python)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be familiar with &lt;strong&gt;image processing&lt;/strong&gt;, imaging techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have a strong interest and motivation for &lt;strong&gt;sustainability and agroecology&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possess advanced &lt;strong&gt;collaborative and interpersonal skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be &lt;strong&gt;fluent in English&lt;/strong&gt; (written and spoken)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;supervision&#34;&gt;Supervision&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our primary goal is for our students to succeed by helping them to develop and achieve their career goals. As such, we support and help students in taking the project in their own direction, within the original scope, and encourage flexibility as well as new viewpoints as the project moves forward. The successful applicant should expect a weekly meeting with &lt;a href=&#34;https://darsa.info/people/auto-qgeissmann&#34;&gt;Quentin Geissmann&lt;/a&gt;, their direct supervisor. Students are encouraged to collaborate within and outside of the group, and will be given (funded) opportunities to present their research at international conferences. We also consider it the supervisor’s role to ensure students feel safe and included in their work environment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;location-and-facilities&#34;&gt;Location and Facilities&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The research takes place in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://qgg.au.dk/en/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;QGG&lt;/a&gt; at &lt;a href=&#34;https://international.au.dk/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Aarhus University (AU)&lt;/a&gt;.
AU is a world-class university (the largest in Denmark), with outstanding opportunities for collaboration on this particular project.
For this project, we have access to various High-Performance Computing platforms and workstations, including GPUs.
In addition to these computational resources, we have  a workshop suitable to prototype hardware (cameras, edge computing, &amp;hellip;) in-house, and have access to larger infrastructure through our collaborations with the engineering department.
Aarhus itself is a vibrant city with an &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.theguardian.com/travel/2016/apr/05/aarhus-denmark-city-of-culture-2017&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;active cultural life&lt;/a&gt;, a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.visitaarhus.com/groups/study-aarhus&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;dynamic student community&lt;/a&gt; and a very high standard of living.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;administrative-considerations&#34;&gt;Administrative Considerations&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;timeline&#34;&gt;Timeline&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The application &lt;strong&gt;deadline is August 31th 2024&lt;/strong&gt;.
The expected start date is &lt;em&gt;January 1st, 2025&lt;/em&gt;, but this is somewhat flexible (as it may depend on personal situations, getting a visa, etc).
The total duration of the PhD is three years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;stipend&#34;&gt;Stipend&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The PhD salaries are set at the university level and defined in &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.hr.aau.dk/digitalAssets/1001/1001827_akademisk_skala_01.04.2021.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;this table&lt;/a&gt; &amp;ndash; the exact numbers depend on previous post-graduate work experience, and the taxation system is somewhat complicated, but expect to have a net salary of approximately 18,000 DKK (≈2,400 Euro) per month. Overall, Denmark is one of the countries where students &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.studyinternational.com/news/highest-phd-stipend/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;earn the most&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;application-process&#34;&gt;Application Process&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In order to ensure a fair assessment of all applicants, the graduate school implements an official procedure. Please refer to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://phd.tech.au.dk/for-applicants/apply-here/saeropslag/phd-in-agricultural-ecology-and-machine-learning-an-underground-video-tracking-system-to-characterise-novel-earthworm-plant-interactions&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;formal offer on the university&amp;rsquo;s website&lt;/a&gt;, which will direct you to an online form.
Candidates will be evaluated based on their CV, motivation statement, and reference letters. Shortlisted candidates will be invited for an interview (online or in person). The top candidate will be offered the position.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;questions&#34;&gt;Questions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, do not hesitate to &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:qgeissmann@qgg.au.dk&#34;&gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt; if you have questions, or want to discuss your interest, ideas&amp;hellip; When doing so, please &lt;em&gt;enclose a CV and a brief description of your motivation&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ANTENNA</title>
      <link>https://darsa.info/project/antenna/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://darsa.info/project/antenna/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;ANTENNA&amp;rdquo; is a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.biodiversa.eu/2022/10/07/2022-2023-joint-call/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;biodiversa+&lt;/a&gt; project conducted by a European consortium (with leading scientists from Germany, Netherlands (Naturalis), Spain, Denmark, Ireland and Greece).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our overarching goal is to develop &lt;strong&gt;modern technologies, such as robotics, computer vision, and molecular methods&lt;/strong&gt; to complement traditional approaches, and ultimately help overcome key &lt;strong&gt;pollinator monitoring gaps&lt;/strong&gt;. The Role of DARSA in ANTENNA is to develop open-source, and readily usable camera-based and citizen-science methods to increase taxonomic and geographic coverage, speed, accuracy, content and efficiency of identification, and temporal resolution of pollinator monitoring.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global Worming</title>
      <link>https://darsa.info/project/global-worming/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://darsa.info/project/global-worming/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Global Worming&amp;rdquo; is five-year &lt;a href=&#34;https://researchleaderprogramme.com/recipients/quentin-geissmann/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;NNF-funded project&lt;/a&gt; that aims to develop &lt;strong&gt;novel deep learning and remote sensing to reveal the uncharted biology of earthworms: cryptic, but pivotal, actors of agroecological circularity&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our food system ultimately rests on soils to produce almost all calories and nutrients. However, agriculture, urban expansion and climate-change-induced desertification are leading to an almost irreversible, alarming and large-scale soil loss. As part of our green transition, farming must become less extractive, more restorative and circular. This change of paradigm must translate into much more research on the processes and organisms, such as decomposers, that enact circularity – which have hitherto been severely understudied. Amongst them, earthworms (EWs), with their unmatched ubiquity and biomass, are pivotal actors. However, these cryptic animals live below ground, making their study a methodological challenge. As a result, we know poorly the behaviour of EWs, their relationships with plants, and their importance in agriculture. With recent technological leaps, we have unprecedented opportunities to open the EW black box. &lt;strong&gt;This project aims to develop unique and novel tools to study EWs in agroecological contexts&lt;/strong&gt;. Using remote sensing and artificial intelligence, we address three difficult tasks that have, so far, hindered EW research: high-throughput species identification, automatic behavioural analysis, and real-time activity monitoring in the field. Throughout, we use these tools to understand how plants, in particular cover crops (a major soil protection tool), and EWs interact.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>InsectAI</title>
      <link>https://darsa.info/collaborators/insectai/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://darsa.info/collaborators/insectai/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PhD Position in Deep Learning for Biodiversity Monitoring: Custom Imaging Platform and Deep Learning to Classify and Phenotype Earthworms</title>
      <link>https://darsa.info/post/2023-vermiscope-phd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://darsa.info/post/2023-vermiscope-phd/</guid>
      <description>















&lt;figure  id=&#34;figure-custom-imaging-platform-and-deep-learning-to-identify-and-phenotype-earthworms&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;d-flex justify-content-center&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;w-100&#34; &gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://darsa.info/deep_worming.webp&#34; alt=&#34;Custom Imaging Platform and Deep Learning to Identify and Phenotype Earthworms&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; data-zoomable /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      Custom Imaging Platform and Deep Learning to Identify and Phenotype Earthworms
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;open-phd-position&#34;&gt;Open PhD Position&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please also see the &lt;a href=&#34;https://phd.tech.au.dk/for-applicants/apply-here/saeropslag/phd-in-deep-learning-for-biodiversity-monitoring-custom-imaging-platform-and-deep-learning-to-classify-and-phenotype-earthworms&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;official posting&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;strong&gt;Deadline: 30 September 2023&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;project-summary&#34;&gt;Project Summary&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This exciting PhD opportunity aims at developing &lt;strong&gt;novel imaging methods and deep learning algorithms to describe and classify earthworms&lt;/strong&gt;. Although cryptic, earthworms have considerable ecological importance, and this original approach will help understand and protect them. It is the first part of &lt;a href=&#34;https://researchleaderprogramme.com/recipients/quentin-geissmann/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;a larger 5-year project&lt;/a&gt; that uses novel technologies (imaging, acoustics, deep learning, remote sensing, etc) to monitor and understand earthworms better.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;project-description&#34;&gt;Project Description&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;context&#34;&gt;Context&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our food system ultimately rests on soils, which we are losing at an alarming rate. To counteract this trend, we need to transition from an extractive to a restorative and &lt;strong&gt;circular agriculture&lt;/strong&gt;. This change of paradigm must come together with more research on the organisms, such as decomposers, that enact circularity – which have so far been severely understudied. Amongst these earthworms, with their unmatched ubiquity and biomass, are pivotal actors. However, these animals live below ground, making their study &lt;strong&gt;a methodological challenge&lt;/strong&gt;: they are very difficult to observe and monitor. However, recent technological developments in remote sensing and deep learning represent an unprecedented opportunity to shed new light on these cryptic actors of circularity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;outcomes&#34;&gt;Outcomes&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The successful applicant will create &lt;strong&gt;design a new acquisition platform&lt;/strong&gt; to &lt;strong&gt;create a large dataset&lt;/strong&gt; of standardized earthworm images. Based on these images, the PhD candidate will &lt;strong&gt;develop novel deep learning&lt;/strong&gt; algorithms to model the &amp;ldquo;grammar of earthworm segments&amp;rdquo;  and automatically classify earthworm species. In addition, this algorithm will explain the anatomy and texture of earthworms to &lt;strong&gt;reveal more cryptic traits&lt;/strong&gt; and eventually study the important variables that affect earthworm diversity, anatomy and development. The prototype imaging and classification tools created during this project may &lt;strong&gt;transform the way we survey earthworms&lt;/strong&gt;, towards a large amount of consistent data, and altogether, greatly facilitate our understanding of these animals as well as our conservation efforts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;research-group&#34;&gt;Research Group&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The successful student will be integrated the growing &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://darsa.info/&#34;&gt;Digital Approaches for Resilient and Sustainable Agriculture (DARSA) group&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, started in 2022, at the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://qgg.au.dk/en&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Center for Quantitative Genetics and Genomics (QGG)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. Both the group and the centre are inclusive and multidisciplinary environments with a range of local and international collaborations. The research takes place at &lt;a href=&#34;https://international.au.dk&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Aarhus University&lt;/a&gt;, a world-leading institution located in a vibrant city.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;applicants-profile-and-eligibility&#34;&gt;Applicant&amp;rsquo;s Profile and Eligibility&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We believe that diversity makes us &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.pnas.org/doi/abs/10.1073/pnas.1700616114&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;better at tackling complex problems&lt;/a&gt;.
Therefore, we strongly support applicants with a diverse background and are committed to promote inclusion and equity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overall, we expect the applicant to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hold a &lt;strong&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s degree&lt;/strong&gt; in data science, mathematics, physics, engineering or another quantitative field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be at least familiar with &lt;strong&gt;hardware design&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;deep learning&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;image processing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have &lt;strong&gt;strong software and/or hardware engineering skills&lt;/strong&gt; (in particular, experience working with scientific languages (&lt;em&gt;e.g.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;code&gt;Python&lt;/code&gt;) and packages (&lt;em&gt;e.g.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;code&gt;Pytorch&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;Tensorflow&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;Scikit-learn&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;Numpy&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;Pandas&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;OpenCV&lt;/code&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have a &lt;strong&gt;strong interest in biodiversity&lt;/strong&gt; (in particular invertebrates)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be &lt;strong&gt;fluent in English&lt;/strong&gt; (written and spoken)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrate advanced &lt;strong&gt;collaborative&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;interpersonal skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;supervision&#34;&gt;Supervision&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our primary goal is for our students to succeed by helping them to develop and achieve their career goals. As such, we support and help students in taking the project in their own direction, within the original scope, and encourage flexibility as well as new viewpoints as the project moves forward. The successful applicant should expect a weekly meeting with &lt;a href=&#34;https://darsa.info/people/auto-qgeissmann&#34;&gt;Quentin Geissmann&lt;/a&gt;, their direct supervisor. Students are encouraged to collaborate within and outside of the group, and will be given (funded) opportunities to present their research at international conferences. We also consider it the supervisor’s role to ensure students feel safe and included in their work environment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;location-and-facilities&#34;&gt;Location and Facilities&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The research takes place in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://qgg.au.dk/en/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;QGG&lt;/a&gt; at &lt;a href=&#34;https://international.au.dk/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Aarhus University (AU)&lt;/a&gt;.
AU is a world-class university (the largest in Denmark), with outstanding opportunities for collaboration on this particular project.
For this project, we have access to various High-Performance Computing platforms and workstations, including GPUs.
In addition to these computational resources, we have  a workshop suitable to prototype hardware (cameras, edge computing, &amp;hellip;) in-house, and have access to larger infrastructure through our collaborations with the engineering department.
Aarhus itself is a vibrant city with an &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.theguardian.com/travel/2016/apr/05/aarhus-denmark-city-of-culture-2017&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;active cultural life&lt;/a&gt;, a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.visitaarhus.com/groups/study-aarhus&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;dynamic student community&lt;/a&gt; and a very high standard of living.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;administrative-considerations&#34;&gt;Administrative Considerations&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;timeline&#34;&gt;Timeline&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The application &lt;strong&gt;deadline is September 31th 2022&lt;/strong&gt;.
The expected start date is &lt;em&gt;January 1st, 2024&lt;/em&gt;, but this is somewhat flexible (as it may depend on personal situations, getting a visa, etc).
The total duration of the PhD is three years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;stipend&#34;&gt;Stipend&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The PhD salaries are set at the university level and defined in &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.hr.aau.dk/digitalAssets/1001/1001827_akademisk_skala_01.04.2021.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;this table&lt;/a&gt; &amp;ndash; the exact numbers depend on previous post-graduate work experience, and the taxation system is somewhat complicated, but expect to have a net salary of approximately 18,000 DKK (≈2,400 Euro) per month. Overall, Denmark is one of the countries where students &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.studyinternational.com/news/highest-phd-stipend/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;earn the most&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-to-apply&#34;&gt;How to Apply&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In order to ensure a fair assessment of all applicants, the graduate school implements an official procedure. Please refer to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://phd.tech.au.dk/for-applicants/apply-here/saeropslag/phd-in-deep-learning-for-biodiversity-monitoring-custom-imaging-platform-and-deep-learning-to-classify-and-phenotype-earthworms&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;formal offer on the university&amp;rsquo;s website&lt;/a&gt;, which will direct you to an online form.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;questions&#34;&gt;Questions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, do not hesitate to &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:qgeissmann@qgg.au.dk&#34;&gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt; if you have questions, or want to discuss your interest, ideas&amp;hellip; When doing so, please &lt;em&gt;enclose a CV and a brief description of your motivation&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PhD Position in Machine learning and agricultural ecology: hierarchical deep learning for better automatic pest classification and biodiversity monitoring in agroecosystems</title>
      <link>https://darsa.info/post/2022-novo-phd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://darsa.info/post/2022-novo-phd/</guid>
      <description>















&lt;figure  id=&#34;figure-towards-hierarchical-classification&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;d-flex justify-content-center&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;w-100&#34; &gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://darsa.info/hierachical_classification.webp&#34; alt=&#34;Towards hierarchical classification&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; data-zoomable /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      Towards hierarchical classification
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;open-phd-position&#34;&gt;Open PhD Position&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please also see the &lt;a href=&#34;https://phd.tech.au.dk/for-applicants/apply-here/saeropslag/phd-in-machine-learning-and-agricultural-ecology-hierarchical-deep-learning-for-better-automatic-pest-classification-and-biodiversity-monitoring-in-agroecosystems&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;official posting&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;project-summary&#34;&gt;Project Summary&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This PhD project aims at developing novel algorithms and annotation tools for hierarchical classification, which has profound and immediate applications to both agriculture and ecology.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;project-description&#34;&gt;Project Description&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;context&#34;&gt;Context&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recently, remarkable innovations in deep learning have begun to transform agriculture – arguably, the most impactful human activity on earth. If used appropriately, machine learning and AI have the potential to drive a digital green transition that could &lt;strong&gt;make agriculture more sustainable, resilient and productive&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One increasingly important data-science task in agriculture is image classification, which is crucial for detecting, monitoring, and eventually mitigating the impact of weeds, pests and diseases. When applied to agricultural problems, image classification generally suffers from three important limitations: 1. &lt;strong&gt;low generalisability&lt;/strong&gt; – &lt;em&gt;i.e.&lt;/em&gt;, it translates poorly to new contexts –; 2. &lt;strong&gt;data-hunger&lt;/strong&gt; – &lt;em&gt;i.e.&lt;/em&gt;, large training datasets are required –; and 3. the &lt;strong&gt;lack of accessible implementations&lt;/strong&gt; for practitioners.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As an alternative to the conventional “flat” classification, we propose to &lt;strong&gt;take advantage of the underlying hierarchical taxonomies&lt;/strong&gt; of the predicted classes to constrain them in &lt;em&gt;a priori&lt;/em&gt; trees, a currently underexplored area. As a simplistic illustration, instead of considering oranges, apples and lemons as independent, we may formulate the explicit tree: &lt;code&gt;{{orange, lemon}, apple}&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;em&gt;i.e.&lt;/em&gt; grouping citrus fruits, and embed this representation in the structure of a neural network.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;outcomes&#34;&gt;Outcomes&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The successful applicant will use &lt;strong&gt;already available datasets&lt;/strong&gt; to explore hierarchical classifications and test our hypotheses: &lt;strong&gt;increased prediction generalisability&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;network robustness as well as reducing the amount of data required&lt;/strong&gt;. This project aims to produce both &lt;strong&gt;seminal machine-learning concepts&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;free and open-source tools for real-world problems&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;research-group&#34;&gt;Research Group&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The successful student will integrate the growing &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://darsa.info/&#34;&gt;Digital Approaches for Resilient and Sustainable Agriculture (DARSA) group&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, started in 2022, at the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://qgg.au.dk/en&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Center for Quantitative Genetics and Genomics (QGG)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. Both the group and the centre are inclusive and multidisciplinary environments with a range of local and international collaborations. The research takes place at &lt;a href=&#34;https://international.au.dk&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Aarhus University&lt;/a&gt;, a world-leading institution located in a vibrant city.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;applicants-profile-and-eligibility&#34;&gt;Applicant&amp;rsquo;s Profile and Eligibility&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We believe that diversity makes us &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.pnas.org/doi/abs/10.1073/pnas.1700616114&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;better at tackling complex problems&lt;/a&gt;.
Therefore, we strongly support applicants with a diverse background and are committed to promote inclusion and equity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overall, we expect the applicant to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hold a &lt;strong&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s degree&lt;/strong&gt; in data science, mathematics, physics, computational biology or another quantitative field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be at least familiar with &lt;strong&gt;deep learning&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;image processing&lt;/strong&gt; and general &lt;strong&gt;database architecture&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have &lt;strong&gt;strong programming skills&lt;/strong&gt; (in particular, experience working with scientific languages (&lt;em&gt;e.g.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;code&gt;R&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;Python&lt;/code&gt;) and packages (&lt;em&gt;e.g.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;code&gt;Pytorch&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;Tensorflow&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;Scikit-learn&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;Numpy&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;Pandas&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;OpenCV&lt;/code&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have an &lt;strong&gt;interest in digital and sustainable agriculture and ecology&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be &lt;strong&gt;fluent in English&lt;/strong&gt; (written and spoken)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrate advanced &lt;strong&gt;collaborative&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;interpersonal skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;supervision&#34;&gt;Supervision&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our primary goal is for our students to succeed by helping them to develop and achieve their career goals. As such, we support and help students take the project in their own direction, within the original scope, and encourage flexibility as well as new viewpoints as the project moves forward. The successful applicant should expect a weekly meeting with &lt;a href=&#34;https://darsa.info/people/auto-qgeissmann&#34;&gt;Quentin Geissmann&lt;/a&gt;, their direct supervisor. Students are encouraged to collaborate within and outside of the group, and will be given (funded) opportunities to present their research at international conferences. We also consider it the supervisor&amp;rsquo;s role to ensure students feel safe and included in their work environment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;location-and-facilities&#34;&gt;Location and Facilities&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The research takes place in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://qgg.au.dk/en/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;QGG&lt;/a&gt; at &lt;a href=&#34;https://international.au.dk/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Aarhus University (AU)&lt;/a&gt;.
AU is a world-class university (the largest in Denmark), with outstanding opportunities for collaboration on this particular project.
For this project, we have access to various High-Performance Computing platforms and workstations, including GPUs.
In addition to these computational resources, we are building an &amp;ldquo;AI lab&amp;rdquo; to prototype hardware (cameras, edge computing, &amp;hellip;) in-house, and have access to larger infrastructure through our collaborations with the engineering department.
Aarhus itself is a vibrant city with an &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.theguardian.com/travel/2016/apr/05/aarhus-denmark-city-of-culture-2017&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;active cultural life&lt;/a&gt;, a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.visitaarhus.com/groups/study-aarhus&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;dynamic student community&lt;/a&gt; and a very high standard of living.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;administrative-considerations&#34;&gt;Administrative Considerations&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;timeline&#34;&gt;Timeline&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The application &lt;strong&gt;deadline is December 20th 2022&lt;/strong&gt;.
The expected start date is &lt;em&gt;July 1st, 2023&lt;/em&gt;, but this is somewhat flexible (as it may depend on personal situations, getting a visa, etc).
The total duration of the PhD is three years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;stipend&#34;&gt;Stipend&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The PhD salaries are set at the university level and defined in &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.hr.aau.dk/digitalAssets/1001/1001827_akademisk_skala_01.04.2021.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;this table&lt;/a&gt; &amp;ndash; the exact numbers depend on previous post-graduate work experience, and the taxation system is somewhat complicated, but expect to have a net salary of approximately 18,000 DKK (≈2,400 Euro) per month. Overall, Denmark is one of the countries where students &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.studyinternational.com/news/highest-phd-stipend/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;earn the most&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-to-apply&#34;&gt;How to Apply&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In order to ensure a fair assessment of all applicants, the graduate school implements an official procedure. Please refer to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://phd.tech.au.dk/for-applicants/apply-here/saeropslag/phd-in-machine-learning-and-agricultural-ecology-hierarchical-deep-learning-for-better-automatic-pest-classification-and-biodiversity-monitoring-in-agroecosystems&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;formal offer on the university&amp;rsquo;s website&lt;/a&gt;, which will direct you to an online form.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;questions&#34;&gt;Questions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, do not hesitate to &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:qgeissmann@qgg.au.dk&#34;&gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt; if you have questions, or want to discuss your interest, ideas&amp;hellip; Then, please &lt;em&gt;enclose a CV and a brief description of your motivation&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daphne Chevalier</title>
      <link>https://darsa.info/people/auto-dchevalier/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://darsa.info/people/auto-dchevalier/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;people-dates&#34;&gt; From 2022-09-01 to 2025-01-01&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Daphne is a M.Sc. student in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://piee-lab.landfood.ubc.ca/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;PIEE Lab&lt;/a&gt; at the University of British Columbia in Vancouver, Canada. She is interested in applied approaches for fostering biodiversity. Her background is in engineering.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Daphne&amp;rsquo;s project examines the effects of artificial light at night on insects and bats, with a focus on circadian rhythm.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PIEE Lab</title>
      <link>https://darsa.info/collaborators/piee-lab/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://darsa.info/collaborators/piee-lab/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sticky Pi</title>
      <link>https://darsa.info/project/sticky-pi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://darsa.info/project/sticky-pi/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Wowchemy, the website builder for Hugo</title>
      <link>https://darsa.info/post/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://darsa.info/post/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Wowchemy website builder for Hugo, along with its starter templates, is designed for professional creators, educators, and teams/organizations - although it can be used to create any kind of site&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The template can be modified and customised to suit your needs. It&amp;rsquo;s a good platform for anyone looking to take control of their data and online identity whilst having the convenience to start off with a &lt;strong&gt;no-code solution (write in Markdown and customize with YAML parameters)&lt;/strong&gt; and having &lt;strong&gt;flexibility to later add even deeper personalization with HTML and CSS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can work with all your favourite tools and apps with hundreds of plugins and integrations to speed up your workflows, interact with your readers, and much more&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
















&lt;figure  id=&#34;figure-the-template-is-mobile-first-with-a-responsive-design-to-ensure-that-your-site-looks-stunning-on-every-device&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;d-flex justify-content-center&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;w-100&#34; &gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/wowchemy/wowchemy-hugo-modules/master/academic.png&#34; alt=&#34;The template is mobile first with a responsive design to ensure that your site looks stunning on every device.&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; data-zoomable /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      The template is mobile first with a responsive design to ensure that your site looks stunning on every device.
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;get-started&#34;&gt;Get Started&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;👉 &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/templates/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Create a new site&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;📚 &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/docs/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Personalize your site&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;💬 &lt;a href=&#34;https://discord.gg/z8wNYzb&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Chat with the &lt;strong&gt;Wowchemy community&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;https://discourse.gohugo.io&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hugo community&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🐦 Twitter: &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/wowchemy&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;@wowchemy&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/GeorgeCushen&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;@GeorgeCushen&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/search?q=%23MadeWithWowchemy&amp;amp;src=typed_query&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;#MadeWithWowchemy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;💡 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/wowchemy/wowchemy-hugo-modules/issues&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Request a &lt;strong&gt;feature&lt;/strong&gt; or report a &lt;strong&gt;bug&lt;/strong&gt; for &lt;em&gt;Wowchemy&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;⬆️ &lt;strong&gt;Updating Wowchemy?&lt;/strong&gt; View the &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/docs/hugo-tutorials/update/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Update Tutorial&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/updates/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Release Notes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;crowd-funded-open-source-software&#34;&gt;Crowd-funded open-source software&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To help us develop this template and software sustainably under the MIT license, we ask all individuals and businesses that use it to help support its ongoing maintenance and development via sponsorship.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;-click-here-to-become-a-sponsor-and-help-support-wowchemys-future-httpswowchemycomplans&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/plans/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;❤️ Click here to become a sponsor and help support Wowchemy&amp;rsquo;s future ❤️&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a token of appreciation for sponsoring, you can &lt;strong&gt;unlock &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/plans/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;these&lt;/a&gt; awesome rewards and extra features 🦄✨&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;ecosystem&#34;&gt;Ecosystem&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/wowchemy/hugo-academic-cli&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Hugo Academic CLI&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/strong&gt; Automatically import publications from BibTeX&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;inspiration&#34;&gt;Inspiration&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://academic-demo.netlify.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Check out the latest &lt;strong&gt;demo&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; of what you&amp;rsquo;ll get in less than 10 minutes, or &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/user-stories/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;view the &lt;strong&gt;showcase&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; of personal, project, and business sites.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;features&#34;&gt;Features&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Page builder&lt;/strong&gt; - Create &lt;em&gt;anything&lt;/em&gt; with &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/docs/page-builder/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;widgets&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/docs/content/writing-markdown-latex/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;elements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Edit any type of content&lt;/strong&gt; - Blog posts, publications, talks, slides, projects, and more!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Create content&lt;/strong&gt; in &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/docs/content/writing-markdown-latex/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Markdown&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/docs/import/jupyter/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jupyter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/docs/install-locally/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RStudio&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Plugin System&lt;/strong&gt; - Fully customizable &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/docs/customization/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;color&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;font themes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Display Code and Math&lt;/strong&gt; - Code highlighting and &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikibooks.org/wiki/LaTeX/Mathematics&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;LaTeX math&lt;/a&gt; supported&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Integrations&lt;/strong&gt; - &lt;a href=&#34;https://analytics.google.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Google Analytics&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://disqus.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Disqus commenting&lt;/a&gt;, Maps, Contact Forms, and more!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Beautiful Site&lt;/strong&gt; - Simple and refreshing one page design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Industry-Leading SEO&lt;/strong&gt; - Help get your website found on search engines and social media&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Media Galleries&lt;/strong&gt; - Display your images and videos with captions in a customizable gallery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mobile Friendly&lt;/strong&gt; - Look amazing on every screen with a mobile friendly version of your site&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multi-language&lt;/strong&gt; - 34+ language packs including English, 中文, and Português&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multi-user&lt;/strong&gt; - Each author gets their own profile page&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Privacy Pack&lt;/strong&gt; - Assists with GDPR&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stand Out&lt;/strong&gt; - Bring your site to life with animation, parallax backgrounds, and scroll effects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;One-Click Deployment&lt;/strong&gt; - No servers. No databases. Only files.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;themes&#34;&gt;Themes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wowchemy and its templates come with &lt;strong&gt;automatic day (light) and night (dark) mode&lt;/strong&gt; built-in. Alternatively, visitors can choose their preferred mode - click the moon icon in the top right of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://academic-demo.netlify.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Demo&lt;/a&gt; to see it in action! Day/night mode can also be disabled by the site admin in &lt;code&gt;params.toml&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/docs/customization&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Choose a stunning &lt;strong&gt;theme&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;font&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; for your site. Themes are fully customizable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;license&#34;&gt;License&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Copyright 2016-present &lt;a href=&#34;https://georgecushen.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;George Cushen&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Released under the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/wowchemy/wowchemy-hugo-modules/blob/master/LICENSE.md&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;MIT&lt;/a&gt; license.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slides</title>
      <link>https://darsa.info/slides/example/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://darsa.info/slides/example/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;create-slides-in-markdown-with-wowchemy&#34;&gt;Create slides in Markdown with Wowchemy&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Wowchemy&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&#34;https://owchemy.com/docs/managing-content/#create-slides&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Documentation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;features&#34;&gt;Features&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Efficiently write slides in Markdown&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-in-1: Create, Present, and Publish your slides&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supports speaker notes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile friendly slides&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;controls&#34;&gt;Controls&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Next: &lt;code&gt;Right Arrow&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;Space&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous: &lt;code&gt;Left Arrow&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Start: &lt;code&gt;Home&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Finish: &lt;code&gt;End&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Overview: &lt;code&gt;Esc&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Speaker notes: &lt;code&gt;S&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fullscreen: &lt;code&gt;F&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Zoom: &lt;code&gt;Alt + Click&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://revealjs.com/pdf-export/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;PDF Export&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;code-highlighting&#34;&gt;Code Highlighting&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Inline code: &lt;code&gt;variable&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Code block:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-python&#34; data-lang=&#34;python&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;n&#34;&gt;porridge&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;s2&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;blueberry&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;k&#34;&gt;if&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;n&#34;&gt;porridge&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;==&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;s2&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;blueberry&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;    &lt;span class=&#34;nb&#34;&gt;print&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s2&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;Eating...&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;math&#34;&gt;Math&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In-line math: $x + y = z$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Block math:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
f\left( x \right) = ;\frac{{2\left( {x + 4} \right)\left( {x - 4} \right)}}{{\left( {x + 4} \right)\left( {x + 1} \right)}}
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;fragments&#34;&gt;Fragments&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Make content appear incrementally&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-fallback&#34; data-lang=&#34;fallback&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;{{% fragment %}} One {{% /fragment %}}
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;{{% fragment %}} **Two** {{% /fragment %}}
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;{{% fragment %}} Three {{% /fragment %}}
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Press &lt;code&gt;Space&lt;/code&gt; to play!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class=&#34;fragment &#34; &gt;
  One
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&#34;fragment &#34; &gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Two&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&#34;fragment &#34; &gt;
  Three
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A fragment can accept two optional parameters:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;class&lt;/code&gt;: use a custom style (requires definition in custom CSS)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;weight&lt;/code&gt;: sets the order in which a fragment appears&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;speaker-notes&#34;&gt;Speaker Notes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Add speaker notes to your presentation&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-markdown&#34; data-lang=&#34;markdown&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;{{% speaker_note %}}
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;k&#34;&gt;-&lt;/span&gt; Only the speaker can read these notes
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;k&#34;&gt;-&lt;/span&gt; Press &lt;span class=&#34;sb&#34;&gt;`S`&lt;/span&gt; key to view
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;  {{% /speaker_note %}}
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Press the &lt;code&gt;S&lt;/code&gt; key to view the speaker notes!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;aside class=&#34;notes&#34;&gt;
  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Only the speaker can read these notes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Press &lt;code&gt;S&lt;/code&gt; key to view&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;/aside&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;themes&#34;&gt;Themes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;black: Black background, white text, blue links (default)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;white: White background, black text, blue links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;league: Gray background, white text, blue links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;beige: Beige background, dark text, brown links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;sky: Blue background, thin dark text, blue links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;night: Black background, thick white text, orange links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;serif: Cappuccino background, gray text, brown links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;simple: White background, black text, blue links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;solarized: Cream-colored background, dark green text, blue links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;section data-noprocess data-shortcode-slide
  
      
      data-background-image=&#34;/media/boards.jpg&#34;
  &gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;custom-slide&#34;&gt;Custom Slide&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Customize the slide style and background&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-markdown&#34; data-lang=&#34;markdown&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;{{&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;slide&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;na&#34;&gt;background-image&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;/media/boards.jpg&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;}}
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;{{&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;slide&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;na&#34;&gt;background-color&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;#0000FF&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;}}
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;{{&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;slide&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;na&#34;&gt;class&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;my-style&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;}}
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;custom-css-example&#34;&gt;Custom CSS Example&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s make headers navy colored.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Create &lt;code&gt;assets/css/reveal_custom.css&lt;/code&gt; with:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-css&#34; data-lang=&#34;css&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nc&#34;&gt;reveal&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;section&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;h1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nc&#34;&gt;reveal&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;section&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;h2&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nc&#34;&gt;reveal&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;section&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;h3&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;  &lt;span class=&#34;k&#34;&gt;color&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;kc&#34;&gt;navy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;questions&#34;&gt;Questions?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/wowchemy/wowchemy-hugo-modules/discussions&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Ask&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/docs/managing-content/#create-slides&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Documentation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ethoscope</title>
      <link>https://darsa.info/project/ethoscope/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://darsa.info/project/ethoscope/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An example conference paper</title>
      <link>https://darsa.info/publication/example/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://darsa.info/publication/example/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Click the &lt;em&gt;Cite&lt;/em&gt; button above to demo the feature to enable visitors to import publication metadata into their reference management software.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Create your slides in Markdown - click the &lt;em&gt;Slides&lt;/em&gt; button to check out the example.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Supplementary notes can be added here, including &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/docs/writing-markdown-latex/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;code, math, and images&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenCFU</title>
      <link>https://darsa.info/project/opencfu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://darsa.info/project/opencfu/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://darsa.info/admin/config.yml</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://darsa.info/admin/config.yml</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
