<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>deep_learning | DARSA</title>
    <link>https://darsa.info/tag/deep_learning/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://darsa.info/tag/deep_learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>deep_learning</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://darsa.info/media/icon_hua8526f2966cb9e7d5f57c97e290bdf30_76380_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>deep_learning</title>
      <link>https://darsa.info/tag/deep_learning/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>DWARPH</title>
      <link>https://darsa.info/project/dwarph/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://darsa.info/project/dwarph/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;DWARPH is a 3-year &lt;a href=&#34;https://dff.dk/en/front-page?set_language=en&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;DFF Sapere-Aude&lt;/a&gt; project on aiming at automating duckweed growth and observation to perform experiment on plant biology at high-throughput.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Plants live in multivariate environments (light, temperature, etc.), ultimately constraining their fitness. Although “phenomics” upscales the measurement of fitness (i.e., the “response”), most work only considers a few environmental values. “Metaphenomics”, instead, integrates whole response “surfaces” (RSs)—over a range of environments—, providing novel insight into plasticity, specialisation and resilience. However, conceptual and methodological limitations have so far hindered the study of RSs. Our three-part project presents a novel paradigm to tackle this issue. i) We use duckweed, a tiny, fast-growing plant and develop an automatic miniature growth chamber that scores growth and can update itself. ii) We create an AI-inspired methodology that plans experiments in real time. iii) We describe the RSs of a genetically diverse duckweed panel to discover the structure and basic biology of RSs. Altogether, our project sheds light on unexplored aspects of plant biology.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sticky Pi</title>
      <link>https://darsa.info/project/sticky-pi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://darsa.info/project/sticky-pi/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
